<!DOCTYPE document PUBLIC
        "-//Apache Software Foundation//DTD XDOC 1.0//EN"
        "http://maven.apache.org/dtd/xdoc_1_0.dtd">
<document>
    <properties>
        <title>Java Pairing-Based Cryptography Library : Docs - Multilinear Maps</title>
        <author email="decaro@dia.unisa.it">Angelo De Caro</author>
    </properties>

    <body>
        <section name="Multilinear Pairing Parameters Generators">

            <p>
            We currently do not have candidates for multilinear
            maps between groups with cryptographically hard problems. However, Garg,
            Gentry, and Halevi (henceforth GGH) suggest a concrete candidate for an
            <span class="em">approximation</span> of multilinear maps, named <span class="em">graded encoding systems</span>.
            With the GGH candidate, group elements have a randomized (and thus non-unique) representation
            dubbed <span class="em">encoding</span>. While it is possible to extract a unique
            <span class="em">canonical bistring</span>, it is not possible to perform further computations
            with this extracted bitstring. An encoding can be re-randomized (e.g., to hide
            the sequence of operations that were performed), but only at the cost of introducing an
            artificial <span class="em">noice</span> term in the encoding. Further operation
            on this group element cause the noise to grow; once this
            noise grows beyond a certain bound, encodings can no longer be worked with.
            </p>


            <a name="ctl13"/>
            <subsection name="CTL13">
                <p>
                    Coron, Lepoint, and Tibouchi4

                Our main contribution is to describe a dierent construction that works over
                the integers instead of ideal lattices, similar to the DGHV fully homomorphic encryption scheme
                [DGHV10] and its batch variant [CCK+13]. Our construction oers the same
                exibility as the
                original from [GGH13]; in particular it can be modied to support the analogue of asymmetric
                maps and composite-order maps. Moreover, it does not seem vulnerable to the \zeroizing" attack
                that breaks base group hardness assumptions like the analogues of DLIN and subgroup membership
                for the multilinear maps of [GGH13]. Since those assumptions are believed necessary to adapt
                constructions of primitives like adaptively secure functional encryption and NIZK, our construction
                seems even more promising for applications than [GGH13]. In Appendix C, we provide a comparison
                with the original scheme, to better highlight the similarities
                </p>

            </subsection>


        </section>
    </body>
</document>
